[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas：所以，这是一个与第一个类似的问题。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: So, this is a problem similar to the first one.
我们将创建一个函数来创建发布订阅对象，并且
We're going to make a function that makes a publish subscribe object, and
它将以正确的顺序可靠地将所有出版物交付给所有订阅者。
it will reliably deliver all publications to all subscribers in the right order.
所以，我们的想法是，我们的系统中可能有多个方面在运行，
So, the idea is that we might have multiple parties running in our system,
他们需要能够相互沟通，我们将为他们提供
and they need to be able to communicate with each other, and we will provide them
它们都将共享的pub子实例，允许它们进行通信。
a pub sub-instance that they will all share, that allows them to communicate.
但是，我们希望确保它正常工作
But, we want to make sure that it works correctly so
它可以正确的顺序可靠地将所有消息传递给每个人。
that it can reliably deliver all the messages to everybody in the right order.
所以，这就是它可能的工作方式。
So, this is how it might work.
我们将有我们的pubsub构造函数，它将创建一个pubsub实例，
We'll have our pubsub constructor, which will make a pubsub instance,
然后我们与所有各方分享。
which we then share with all the parties.
它将在其上具有Subscribe方法，该方法可以接收函数，
It will have a subscribe method on it which can receive a function,
每当有人发布时都会调用它，他们可以通过调用
which will be called whenever somebody publishes, and they can publish by calling
Publish方法，该方法随后将导致调用所有订阅者。
the publish method, which will then cause all of the subscribers to get called.
好的，所以你可以想象
Okay, so you can imagine how you might
实现这样的东西并不是很复杂。
implement something like that it's not very complicated.
下面是一个可能的实现。
Here is a possible implementation.
我们有一个pub子构造函数，它有一个订阅者数组
We've got a pub sub constructor, it has an array of subscribers where it's going to
保留完整的订阅者列表。
keep the full list of subscribers.
它将返回一个包含两个方法的对象。
It will return an object containing two methods.
首先，Subscribe方法将接收一个订阅者，并且
First the subscribe method will receive a subscriber and
将其推送到订阅者列表中，他们的发布方法将
push it onto the subscribers list, and they publish method will
循环遍历所有订阅者，并呼叫每个订阅者并将消息传递给他们。
Loop through all of the subscribers and call each one and give them the message.
好的，看起来很简单，而且
Okay, so looks pretty straightforward, and
不幸的是，它没有做任何我们需要保证的事情。
unfortunately it doesn't do any of the things that we need to guarantee.
可以防止人们发布和订阅。
It is possible to prevent people from publishing and subscribing.
可以，&gt；&gt；Douglas：删除订阅者和
It's possible to, &gt;&gt; Douglas: Remove subscribers and
导致消息被无序传递。
cause messages to get delivered out of order.
这本应防止的一切
Everything that this is supposed to prevent
它会允许的，所以你的工作就是找出攻击者是如何做到这一点的。
It will allow, so your job is to figure out how an attacker can do this.
因此，如果攻击者是其中一个订阅者，并且想要将其搞砸
So, if an attacker is one of the subscribers and wants to screw it up for
所有其他订阅者，他是怎么做到的？
all the other subscribers, how does he do that?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：他使用了之前的攻击，并且
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: He used the attack from before, and
清空订阅者，对吗？
empty out the subscribers, right?
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：这是需要关注的事情，
&gt;&gt; Douglas: That is something to be concerned about,
这次我们没有存储方法。
we don't have a store method this time.
所以，我们没有提供改变推力的方法
So, we don't provide a way of changing the push
属性，但这绝对是
property of the subscribers array, but that's definitely
你想要思考的事情&GT；&GT；演讲者3：什么
something you want to be thinking about &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Whats
现在发布的功能？
the function now publishing?
对不起，如果您按下一个叫做Publish的函数，
Sorry, if you push a function called publish,
不是因为我们的反应是垃圾。
it's not because our response because it's crap.
如果你推送一个功能，两周的订阅者
If you push a function that two weeks subscribers for
例子是这样的，因为这个。
example is like this because this.
等你找到我
When you get to me,
我刚才推的那个是你叫订阅者眼睛时的一个函数。
the one I just pushed which is a function when you call subscribers eye.
你呼吁出版，你现在可以访问这个。
You call on publication, you now have access to this.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：你完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: You are exactly right.
不幸的是，Powerpoint迫使我强迫您做而不是特定
Unfortunately, Powerpoint compels me to force you to do the instead of particular
订单，所以请记住，我们会回来的，好吗？
order So please remember that we will come back to it okay?
&gt；&gt；[INAUDIBLE]&gt；&gt；Douglas：是的，
&gt;&gt; [INAUDIBLE] &gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah,
我在这里是PPT的奴隶。
I'm a slave to PowerPoint here.
是的，所以我们不得不这么做。
Yeah, so we're gonna have to do that.
所以我们必须这么做，但是
So we're gonna have to, but
我会再次呼吁你这样做，因为你是绝对正确的。
I will call on you to do that again because you are absolutely right.
&gt；&gt；[INAUDIBLE]&gt；&gt；Douglas：SO
&gt;&gt; [INAUDIBLE] &gt;&gt; Douglas: So
让我们从如何防止其他人接收消息开始。
let's start with how can I prevent other people from receiving messages.
你之前差点就成功了。
You almost had it earlier.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：所以一个函数，叫做Publish。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So a function, call it publish.
然后覆盖它。
Then overwrite it.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：不，这要容易得多。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: No, it's much easier than that.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 4：这是否会在下次发布时立即失败或
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Will this fail immediately on the next publish or
在下一次发布之后的发布之前，它不会失败吗？
will it not fail until the publish after the next publish?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：它应该立即失败&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：你会立即失败。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: It should fail immediately &gt;&gt; Douglas: You'll fail instantly.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：很抱歉，它将在下一次发布时失败。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: I'm sorry, it will fail on the next publication.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：我可以设置发布，&gt；&gt；扬声器4：可以吗
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: I can just set publish, &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Can I
只是将PUBLISH设置为NULL吗？
just set publish equal to null?
&gt；&gt；Douglas：是的，不幸的是Power Point迫使我
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Yes, unfortunately Power Point compels me to
让你也记住这一点。
ask you to remember that one too.
我试着预测人们拿出这些东西的顺序
I try to anticipate what order people to come up with these
和&gt；&gt；扬声器4：对不起。
and &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: I'm sorry.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：不，你很好。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: No, you're good.
&gt；&gt；发言人4：我们的任务是破坏
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: We're being tasked with sabotaging for
许多以前呼叫过的那些订阅者都是从获取
many all those subscribers who have previously called subscribe from getting
&gt；&gt；扬声器5：出版商时的出版物
&gt;&gt; Speaker 5: Publications when publishers
叫做。
is called.
好吧。
Okay.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：好的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Okay.
既然你走在我前面让我
So since you're getting way ahead of me let me
让我们先看看我们需要做的那个。
show the one that we need to do first.